Guide to the Spyros P. Skouras Papers M0509
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Series 5: Investments And Projects
  - Xelopan Greece
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Credit Agreement: Cr#C40-9. (Vol.1) (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Credit Agreement: Cr#C40-'9 (Vol.2) (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Credit Agreement: Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Export-Import Bank Of Washington: Correspondence - general (Box 56, Folder 11)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Guaranty Agreement Aid- JCP-TAP-SPS (Box 56, Folder 12)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: Letter Agreement JCP-TAP-SPS (Box 56, Folder 13)
    - Legal - Contracts And Agreements: License - Greek Govt. - Correspondence (Box 56, Folder 14)
    - Legal - Letters Of Agreement: Withdrawal by SPS, release and indemnity JCP-TAP and C. Pappas Co. (Box 56, Folder 15)
    - Legal - Letters of Agreement: License - Greek Govt (Box 56, Folder 16)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex Md. ) Pappas, John C. & Skouras, Spyros P., 1961 (Box 57, Folder 1)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex Md. ) Pappas, John C. & Skouras, Spyros P., 1/15/62 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex Md. ) Pappas, John C. & Skouras, Spyros P.: Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex) Pappas, John C. & Skouras S.P.: correspondence (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Finance - Financial Statements - Re: Proposed Wallboard Plants (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Finance - Report/Feasibility - Little, Arthur D. (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Finance - Reports And Correspondence (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Publications: International Construction Reporter (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex) Pappas, John C. & Skouras S.P.: Supplemental Data 1 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Finance - Loan Application (Formerly Xelotex) Pappas, John C. & Skouras S.P.: Supplemental Data 2 (Box 57, Folder 6)
- Series 6: Ecumenical Patriarchate/GOA
  - Ecumenical Patriarchate
    - General (Box 58, Folder 1)
    - Athenagoras European Trip, 1967 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Fund Raising Campaign (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Patriarchate Of Alexandria (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Patriarchate Of East Jerusalem (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Photographs (Box 58, Folder 6)
    - Rebuilding Campaign (Box 58, Folder 7)
    - 20th Anniversary Of Enthronement (Box 58, Folder 8)
    - United States Government (Correspondence) (Box 58, Folder 9)
    - Visit To Constantinople, 1962 (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - GOA (Greek Orthodox Archdiocese)
    - General (Box 58, Folder 11)
    - Archbishop Lakovos, General (Box 58, Folder 12)
    - H.E. Archbishop Lakovos Nameday Ball (Box 58, Folder 13)
    - Toa Archdiocesan Departments: Biennial Clergy - Laity Congress (Box 58, Folder 14)
    - Toa Archdiocesan Departments: Council (Box 58, Folder 15)
    - Toa Archdiocesan Departments: Endowment Fund (Box 58, Folder 16)
    - Toa Archdiocesan Departments: Mixed Council ~ (Box 58, Folder 17)
    - Recognition Of Greek Orthodox Church As A Major Faith In The U.S.A. (Box 58, Folder 18)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: General (Box 59, Folder 1)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Budget. (Box 59, Folder 2)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Cathedral Ball (Box 59, Folder 3)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Cathedral School (Box 59, Folder 4)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Orthodox Youth (Gova) (Box 59, Folder 5)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Ladies Phi1optohos Society (Box 59, Folder 6)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Real Estate #1 (Box 59, Folder 7)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Real Estate #2~2 (Box 59, Folder 8)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Sustaining Membership (Box 59, Folder 9)
    - Archdiocesan Cathedral Holy Trinity: Board Of Trustees (Box 59, Folder 10)
    - Churches: General (Box 59, Folder 11)
    - Churches: St. Sophia Cathedral, Los Angeles (Box 60, Folder 1)
    - Fraternal Organizations: Knights Of St. Andrew (Box 60, Folder 2)
    - Institutions: Bartholomis Summer Camp In Greece (Box 60, Folder 3)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College (Box 60, Folder 4)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College General (Box 60, Folder 5)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College Finance (Box 60, Folder 6)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College Fundraising Suggestion With Life Magazine (Box 60, Folder 7)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College: Hellenic University. Foundation #1 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College: Hellenic University Foundation #2 (Box 60, Folder 9)
    - Institutions: Hellenic College: Meetings (Box 60, Folder 10)
    - Institutions: Skouras Center For The Creative Arts: Solicitations (Box 60, Folder 11)
    - Institutions: Skouras Center For The Creative Arts: Students And Faculty (Box 60, Folder 12)
    - Institutions: Holy Cross Theological School (Box 61, Folder 1)
    - Institutions: St. Basil's Academy (Box 61, Folder 2)
    - Institutions: St. Michael's Home For The Aged (Box 61, Folder 3)
    - Institutions: General (Box 61, Folder 4)
    - Institutions: Administrative Matters (Box 61, Folder 5)
    - Institutions: Chapters. (Box 61, Folder 6)
    - Institutions: Finance (Box 61, Folder 7)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: "Cactus Flower" Premiere (Box 61, Folder 8)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: "Fiddler On The Roof" Premiere (Box 61, Folder 9)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: "Trojan Women" Premiere (Cancelled) (Box 61, Folder 10)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: Van Fleet Dinner, 1970 (Box 61, Folder 11)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: Mobile Dental Clinic For Greece (Box 61, Folder 12)
    - Institutions: Fund-Raising: Notices, Minutes, Meetings (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Series 7: Organizations & Charities
  - Social
    - Greek Syndicate, No.1 (Box 68, Folder 6)
    - Greek Syndicate, No. 2 (Box 68, Folder 7)
  - Commercial
    - General (Box 62, Folder 1)
    - American Israel Chamber Of Commerce (Box 62, Folder 2)
    - American Turkish Society (Box 62, Folder 3)
    - Eastern Mediterranean Development lnstitute (Box 62, Folder 4)
    - Economic Club Of New York (Box 62, Folder 5)
    - Hellenic American Chamber Of Commerce (Box 62, Folder 6)
    - Investors Of America (Box 62, Folder 7)
    - National Association Of Manufacturers (Box 62, Folder 8)
    - Peruvian American Association (Box 62, Folder 9)
    - Transportation Association (Box 62, Folder 10)
    - United Shareowners Of America, Inc. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Cultural
    - General (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Humanitarian
    - Boys Club Of Queens - Dinner - S.P. Skouras (Box 62, Folder 13)
    - Boys Club Of Queens - Dinner - Man Of The Year Dinner (Box 62, Folder 14)
    - Boys Club Of Queens - Dinner - Sa1a~Hassanein (Box 62, Folder 15)
    - Boys Club Of Queens - Dinner - Cubby Broccoli (Box 62, Folder 16)
    - Boys Town Of Italy (Box 63, Folder 1)
    - Center For Russian Jewry (Box 63, Folder 2)
    - Chilean Earthquake (Box 63, Folder 3)
    - Citizens Committe Forpeace In Vietnam (Box 63, Folder 4)
    - Committee To Support American Servicemen In Vietnam (SAS) (Box 63, Folder 5)
    - Duke Of Edinburgh Award (Box 63, Folder 6)
    - 52 Association (Box 63, Folder 7)
    - Films (Box 63, Folder 8)
    - Freedom Foundation At Valley Forge (Box 63, Folder 9)
    - Grand St. Boys Association (Box 63, Folder 10)
    - Hospitalized Veterans Service (Musicians Emergency Fund) (Box 63, Folder 11)
    - Korea Society (Box 63, Folder 12)
    - Near East Emergency Donations (Need) (Box 63, Folder 13)
    - Recordings For The Blind (Box 63, Folder 14)
    - United Fund Of. Greater New York (Box 63, Folder 15)
    - United Jewish Appeal (Box 63, Folder 16)
    - U.S. Committee For Refugees #1 (Box 63, Folder 17)
    - U.S. Committee For Refugees #2 (Box 63, Folder 18)
    - USO #1 (Box 64, Folder 1)
    - USO #2 (Box 64, Folder 2)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: General, 1966 (Box 64, Folder 3)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: General, 1968 No1 (Box 64, Folder 4)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: General, 1968 No2 (Box 64, Folder 5)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: General, 1969 (Box 64, Folder 6)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: General, l970 (Box 64, Folder 7)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Lord Mountbatten Luncheon & Dinner (Box 64, Folder 8)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Prince Phillip Luncheon (Box 64, Folder 9)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Teamsters Union Pledge, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 1)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Teamsters Union Pledge, 1969-71 (Box 65, Folder 2)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Conventions (Box 65, Folder 3)
    - Variety Clubs: Sunshine Coach Program: Clippings (Box 65, Folder 4)
    - Veterans Of Foreign Wars (Box 65, Folder 5)
    - Vocational Foundation (Box 65, Folder 6)
    - Waif (Children's Division Of Mt. Social Services) (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Political - Republican Party
    - Agnew, Spiro T. Testimonial Dinner (Box 65, Folder 8)
    - Congressmen Brademas & Galifianakis (Box 65, Folder 9)
    - Congressman Halpern, Seymour (Box 65, Folder 10)
    - Congressman Reid, Ogden (Box 65, Folder 11)
    - General #1 (Box 65, Folder 12)
    - General #2 (Box 65, Folder 13)
    - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 66, Folder 1)
    - Keating, Kenneth (Box 66, Folder 2)
    - Lindsay., John V. - Finance Committee (Box 66, Folder 3)
    - Metropolitan Republican Club (Box 66, Folder 4)
    - National Republican Senatorial Committee (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - Nixon - Nixon-Lodge Campaign, 1960 (Box 66, Folder 6)
    - N.Y. Republican State Dinner Committee (Box 66, Folder 7)
    - Republican Center (Box 66, Folder 8)
    - Republican Congressional Boosters Club (Box 66, Folder 9)
    - Republican Dinner For Good Government N.Y.C. (Box 66, Folder 10)
    - Republican National Finance Committee, No. 1 (Box 66, Folder 11)
    - Republican National Finance Committee, No. 2 (Box 66, Folder 12)
    - Republican National Finance Committee, No. 3 (Box 66, Folder 13)
    - Republicans For Progress (Box 66, Folder 14)
    - Republican 1972 "Luck Off" Dinner (Box 66, Folder 15)
    - Repub. Senate House Majority Dinner (Box 66, Folder 16)
    - Republican Victory Dinner (Box 66, Folder 17)
    - Rockefeller Ethnic Group Dinner 1970 (Box 66, Folder 18)
    - Rockefeller, Governor Nelson A. (Box 67, Folder 1)
    - Senator Javits, Jacks K. (Box 67, Folder 2)
    - Senator Percy, Charles (Box 67, Folder 3)
    - Senator, Symington, Stuart (Box 67, Folder 4)
    - Van Cott, George - N.Y. State Assemblyman (Box 67, Folder 5)
  - Religious
    - General (Box 67, Folder 6)
    - American Bible Society (Laymen's National Committee) (Box 67, Folder 7)
    - Brotherhood-In-Action (Box 67, Folder 8)
    - Cardinal's Committee Of The Laity (Box 67, Folder 9)
    - Catholic Interracial Council (Box 67, Folder 10)
    - Church World Service (Box 67, Folder 11)
    - Interfaith Movement, Inc. (Box 67, Folder 12)
    - Laymen's National Bible Committee (Box 67, Folder 13)
    - National Conference Of Christians And Jews (Box 67, Folder 14)
    - Protestant Council Of N.Y. City (Box 68, Folder 1)
    - St. Paul's Society (Box 68, Folder 2)
    - The Salvation Army (Box 68, Folder 3)
    - Smith, (Alfred E.). Memorial Foundation (Box 68, Folder 4)
  - Social
    - Bohemian Encampment (Box 68, Folder 5)
  - Sports
    - General (Box 68, Folder 9)
  - Various
    - General #1 (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - General #2 (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Edison (Thomas Alva) Foundation #1 (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Edison (Thomas Alva) Foundation #2 (Box 69, Folder 1)
    - The Explorers Club (Box 69, Folder 2)
    - Girl Scout. Council Of Greater New York (Box 69, Folder 3)
    - Morality In Media (Box 69, Folder 4)
    - National Parks & Conservation Assn. (Box 69, Folder 5)
    - Near East Foundation (Box 69, Folder 6)
    - The Order Of Lafayette (Box 69, Folder 7)
    - Radio Free Asia (Box 69, Folder 8)
    - Radio Free Europe (Box 69, Folder 9)
    - Society For The Family Of Man (Box 69, Folder 10)
    - Thayer, (Sylvanus) Hall Of Fame Committee (Box 69, Folder 11)
    - United Nations: UNA/USA Concert Dinner, Wash. D.C. #1 (Box 69, Folder 12)
    - United Nations: UNA/USA Concert Dinner, Wash. D.C. #2 (Box 69, Folder 13)
    - United Nations Day Dinner, NY, 1970 (Box 69, Folder 14)
- Series 8: Public Relations
  - Anniversaries
    - General (Box 70, Folder 1)
  - Articles
    - Skouras, Spyros P. -General (Box 70, Folder 2)
  - Awards
    - General (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - AOTOS (Admiral Of The Ocean Seas), Sep-70 (Box 70, Folder 4)
    - Human Relations Award, Oct-62 (Box 70, Folder 5)
    - Morality In Media, Dec-68 (Box 70, Folder 6)
    - Order Of Layfayette, Dec-70 (Box 70, Folder 7)
    - Religious Heritage Of America, "Business Man Of The Year", June 1971 (Box 70, Folder 8)
    - Walt Disney Award, Nov-68 (Box 70, Folder 9)
  - Birthdays
    - Entertainers (Box 70, Folder 10)
    - Friends. (Box 70, Folder 11)
    - Government Officials (Box 70, Folder 12)
    - Relatives (Box 70, Folder 13)
    - Skouras, Spyros P. (Box 70, Folder 14)
  - Civic Activities
    - General (Box 70, Folder 15)
  - Clippings
    - unspecified (Box 70, Folder 16)
  - Condolences
    - Churchill, Winston (Box 70, Folder 17)
    - Family (Box 70, Folder 18)
    - Friends #1 (Box 70, Folder 19)
    - Friends #2 (Box 70, Folder 20)
    - Kennedy Family (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - King Paul Of Greece (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Rockefeller Family (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Skouras, Charles P. (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Skouras, George P. (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - VIPS #1 (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - VIPS #2 (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Commemorative Stamp Issues
    - Commemorative Stamp Issues - General (Box 71, Folder 8)
  - Congratulations
    - Entertainers (Box 71, Folder 9)
    - Family (Box 71, Folder 10)
    - Friends (Box 71, Folder 11)
    - Political (Box 71, Folder 12)
    - Prudential-Grace Acquisition (Box 72, Folder 1)
    - VIPS (Box 72, Folder 2)
  - Educational
    - Modern Greek Studies (Box 72, Folder 3)
  - Endorsements
    - Artists: General (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - Artists: Mu, Helen (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - Artists: Jones, Jennifer (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - Clubs - General (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - Colleges-General (Box 72, Folder 8)
  - Employment
    - General #1 (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - General #2 (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - Allis, Ted (Box 73, Folder 1)
    - Boucles, Dentosthenis (Box 73, Folder 2)
    - Carrera, Edelberto (Box 73, Folder 3)
    - Desmarais, Rene (Box 73, Folder 4)
    - Fusscas James (Box 73, Folder 5)
    - Gibbons, Patrick (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Issachar, Rebecca (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Kacandos, Simo (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Mackenzie, Donald (Box 73, Folder 9)
    - Saytanides, Judge (Box 73, Folder 10)
    - Stahl, Michael (Box 73, Folder 11)
    - Tavricies, Maria (Box 73, Folder 12)
    - Theophilos,Vstephen (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - Tsoucalas, Nicholas (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - Vance, Andrew (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Warshauer, Jacques (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Weinmann, George (Box 73, Folder 17)
  - Entertainment
    - Dinners: General Honoring SPS (Box 73, Folder 18)
    - Dinners: American Israel Chamber Of Commerce (Box 73, Folder 19)
    - Dinners: Caramanlis, Prime Minister Of Greece (Box 73, Folder 20)
    - Dinners: Golden Anniversary SPS (Box 74, Folder 1)
    - Dinners: Papandreou, Prime Minister George (Box 74, Folder 2)
    - Dinners: 75th Jubilee Dinner, Jan., 1969 (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Dinners: 75th Jubilee Dinner, Jan., 1969 (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Invitations extended - General (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Invitations Received: General #1 (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Invitations Received: General #2 (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - Invitations Received: USSR (Box 74, Folder 8)
    - Launchings (Box 74, Folder 9)
    - Luncheons: General (Box 75, Folder 1)
    - Luncheons: Allen, George V., 1961 (Box 75, Folder 2)
    - Luncheons: Menderes, H.E. Adnan (Box 75, Folder 3)
    - Luncheons: Okasha, Dr. UAR, 1960 (Box 75, Folder 4)
    - Luncheons: Younes, Dr. UAR, 1963 (Box 75, Folder 5)
    - Interviews - General (Box 75, Folder 6)
    - Premieres - General (Box 75, Folder 7)
  - Eulogies
    - General (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - Schenck. Joseph (Box 75, Folder 9)
  - Films
    - "Down the Road" & "The Crowning Experience" (Box 75, Folder 9.5)
  - Gifts
    - Gifts - General (Box 75, Folder 10)
  - Greetings
    - Christmas - General (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - Christmas Messages (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - Easter - General (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - Nameday -General (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - New Year - General (Box 75, Folder 15)
  - Honorary Degrees
    - General (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - University Of Tampa (Box 76, Folder 2)
  - Humanitarian Intercession
    - General (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - Merkouris, James (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - Petite, George (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - Phillies, George (Box 76, Folder 6)
  - International Affairs
    - Cyprus Situation (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - Greek Government (After Revolution Of 1967) (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - Greek Government (Box 76, Folder 9)
    - Greek War relief (Box 76, Folder 10)
    - Israel (Box 76, Folder 11)
    - Israe1-~Cyprus Situation (Box 76, Folder 12)
    - Jewish Nationals Greece (Box 76, Folder 13)
    - Mamoulian, Rouben (Box 76, Folder 14)
    - New York World's Fair (Box 76, Folder 15)
    - UAR Sound & Light Festivals Pyramids, Etc. (Box 76, Folder 16)
  - Photographs
    - Photographs - Various (Box 77, Folder 1)
  - Recovery Letters: SPS 1962 Operation
    - Recovery letters, no. 1, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 2)
    - Recovery letters, no. 2, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 3)
    - Recovery letters, no. 3, 1962 (Box 77, Folder 4)
  - Retirement & Resignation
    - Correspondence (Box 77, Folder 5)
  - Special Events
    - General (Box 77, Folder 6)
    - Apollo Launching (Box 77, Folder 7)
    - Greek Independence Parade (Box 77, Folder 8)
    - Inauguration: Eisenhower/Nixon (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - Inauguration: Kennedy/Johnson (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - Inauguration: Nixon/Agnew (Box 77, Folder 11)
    - LBJ Signing Bill Re: Ellis Island (Box 77, Folder 12)
  - Tapes
    - Tapes - General (Box 78, Folder 1)
  - Thank Yous
    - Thank You - General (Box 78, Folder 2)
  - Theater Passes
    - Theatre Passes - General (Box 78, Folder 3)
  - Visits Fox Studios
    - Visits Fox Studios - General (Box 78, Folder 4)
  - USSR
    - General (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Cultural Exchange Agreement With USA (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence With USIA (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Khruschev Luncheon At Studio: Adverse Comments (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Khruschev Luncheon At Studio: Congratulatory Comments (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Reciprocal Premieres_"All About Eve" And "The Idiot" (Box 78, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Exhibit In Moscow (Box 78, Folder 11)
    - Articles By SPS (Box 78, Folder 12)
  - U.S. Government
    - Public relations - General (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Public Comments (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Advertising: General (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Advertising: Tie-in Promotions (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - Awards (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - U.S. Government - various (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - House Un-American Activities Committee (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Request For Films (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - United Arab Republic (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - U.S. Information Agency (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - U.S. Savings Bond Program (Box 79, Folder 11)
- Series 9: Speeches
  - Motion Picture Industry 1948
    - Press Conference SPS, 1948 Jan 22 (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Motion Picture President's Dinner, 1948 Feb 4 (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Opening Remarks By SPS On "Motion Pictures In Education" At The Forum)Boston University, 1948 March 13 (Box 79, Folder 14)
    - Testimonial To Walter Vincent, 1948 May 2 (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - Draft Of Speech For SPS For The Luncheon Of Publishers And Editors, 1948 May 18 (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - Fox Stockholders Report, 1948 (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Remarks To Stockholders, 1948 May 8 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - National Theatre Convention, 1948 Sep (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Suggested Opening Remarks At Sales Meeting, L.A., 1948 Sep (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Suggested Speech For Eric Johnston MPAA Meeting, 1948 Dec 2 (Box 79, Folder 21)
    - Radio Executives Club Of New York, 1948 Dec 30 (Box 79, Folder 22)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1949
    - General Sales Managers Meetings, 1949 March 14, 15 (Box 79, Folder 23)
    - B'nai B'rith Philadelphia, Pa.-Acceptance Of Award Of Merit To Fox, 1949 March 21 (Box 79, Folder 24)
    - Exhibitors And Sales Luncheon, 1949 April 1 (Box 79, Folder 25)
    - Fox Stockholders Meeting, 1949 May 17 (Box 79, Folder 26)
    - All-Industry Meeting Chicago, 1949 Aug 30 (Box 79, Folder 27)
    - Motion Picture Pioneers, 1949 Nov 16 (Box 79, Folder 28)
    - Distribution Conference, 1949 Nov 21 (Box 79, Folder 29)
    - Company Dinner, 1949 Dec 21 (Box 79, Folder 30)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1950
    - 20th Century Fox Second Showmanship Meeting, 1950 Jan 27 (Box 79, Folder 31)
    - Welcome Speech - Showmanship Chicago Meeting: A.M., 1950 March 8 (Box 79, Folder 32)
    - Welcome Speech - Showmanship Chicago Meeting: P.M., 1950 March 8 (Box 79, Folder 33)
    - Showmanship Meeting N.Y. City, 1950 March 23 (Box 79, Folder 34)
    - Society Of Motion Picture And Television Engineers - Chicago, 1950 April 24 (Box 79, Folder 35)
    - Draft Speech To Security Analysts Boston, 1950 May l (Box 79, Folder 36)
    - Uja Notes Executive Meeting, 1950 May 9 (Box 79, Folder 37)
    - Draft Of Speech For Rome, 1950 June (Box 79, Folder 38)
    - Freedom House -~ Acceptance Of Award For "No Way Out ", 1950 Aug 23 (Box 79, Folder 39)
    - TOA Convention In Houston, 1950 Oct 31 (Box 79, Folder 40)
    - Pioneers Dinner In Honor Of SPS, 1950 Nov 1 (Box 79, Folder 41)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1951
    - Company Executive. Dinner Meeting, 1951 Jan 3 (Box 80, Folder 1)
    - Compo Luncheon, 1951 Feb 23 (Box 80, Folder 2)
    - Philadelphia Fellowship Commission Award To Fox, 1951 March (Box 80, Folder 3)
    - Notes From Meeting (Fox), 1951 April 3 (Box 80, Folder 4)
    - "Are Movies Better Than Ever" By SPS, Harvard School, 1951 April 13 (Box 80, Folder 5)
    - Annual Meeting Of Stockholders-SPS Report, 1951 May 15 (Box 80, Folder 6)
    - Los Angelessales Convention, 1951 June 11 (Box 80, Folder 7)
    - Sales Convention L.A., 1951 June 15 (Box 80, Folder 8)
    - Speech To Exhibitors For Recording, 1951 July 24 (Box 80, Folder 9)
    - Compo Meeting -. Inaugurating Movietime USA, 1951 Sep 6 (Box 80, Folder 10)
    - Special meeting Of Stockholders, 1951 Oct 4 (Box 80, Folder 11)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1952
    - Welcome Address By Sf5 - Sales Convention, 1952 Jan 7 (Box 80, Folder 12)
    - Sales Convention - NYC, 1952 Jan 11 (Box 80, Folder 13)
    - Presentation Of Plaque For "David & Bathsheba" To Fox, 1952 March 11 (Box 80, Folder 14)
    - Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1952 May 20 (Box 80, Folder 15)
    - Sales Managers Speech, 1952 June 27 (Box 80, Folder 16)
    - SPS' Report To Executive And Development Heads, 1952 Dec 29 (Box 80, Folder 17)
  - Motion Picture Industry 1953
    - Acceptance Speech By SPS For "The Christophers Award" To Our Film "Stars And Stripes Forever", 1953 Jan14 (Box 80, Folder 18)
    - SPS Accepting Award For Motion Picture Industry At Dinner For NCoCJ, 1953 Feb 19 (Box 80, Folder 19)
    - Notes On SPS Press Conference, 1953 April 16 (Box 80, Folder 20)
    - Address By SPS At Annual Stockholders Meeting, 1953 May 19 (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - Annual Report To Stockholders, 1953 May 19 (Box 80, Folder 22)